本字幕由 YYeTs人人影视 翻译创作
欢迎爱好者加入我们  www.YYeTs.net
■
翻译：yuyuye
校对&监制：吕黎  后期：☆☆
■
闪灵
面试
你好  我跟厄尔曼先生有预约
Hi. I've got an appointment with Mr. Ullman.
我叫杰克·托伦斯
My name is Jack Torrance.
他的办公室在左边第一个门
His office is the first door on the left.
谢谢
Thank you.
-是厄尔曼先生吗  -是的
- Mr. Ullman? - Yeah?
我是杰克·托伦斯
I'm Jack Torrance.
快进来  杰克
Come on in, Jack.
-很高兴见到你  -很高兴见到你
- Very nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
这位是我的秘书  苏茜
This is my secretary, Susie.
-苏茜  你好吗  -我们这儿难找吗
- Susie, how do you do? - Any trouble finding us?
一点都不难找  到这儿花了3个半小时
No problem at all. Made the trip in three and a half hours.
路途还蛮远的嘛
That's very good time.
坐吧  杰克
Sit down a minute, Jack.
别拘束
Just make yourself at home.
要喝咖啡吗
Like some coffee?
如果有咖啡的话  就给我来一杯  谢谢
If you're having some, I wouldn't mind. Thanks.
-苏茜  -好的
- Susie. - Sure.
还有  叫比尔·沃森进来
And ask Bill Watson to join us.
好的
Yes, I will.
妈妈
Mom?
什么事
Yeah?
你确定要去住那间酒店过冬吗
Do you really wanna go and live in that hotel for the winter?
当然
Sure I do.
会很有趣的
It'll be lots of fun.
我猜是吧
Yeah. I guess so.
不管怎样  那儿附近几乎没有玩伴
Anyway, there's hardly anybody to play with around here.
是  我知道  总要花点时间才能交到新朋友
Yeah, I know. It always takes a little time to make new friends.
也许吧
Yeah, I guess so.
托尼呢
What about Tony?
我肯定  他很期待住酒店
He's looking forward to the hotel, I bet.
不  我不想去  托伦斯太太
No, ain't, Mrs. Torrance.
得了吧  托尼  别傻了
Now, come on, Tony. Don't be silly.
我不想去那儿
I don't wanna go there.
你怎么会不想去呢
How come you don't wanna go?
我就是不想
I just don't.
他们有跟你讲过在丹佛的
Did they give you any idea in Denver...
相关工作需要吗
...about what the job entails?
简单介绍了一下而已
Only in a very general way.
冬季可能会非常难以忍受
The winters can be fantastically cruel.
基本意思就是要应付非常昂贵的损失
The basic idea is to cope with the very costly damage...
以及可能发生的贬值
...and depreciation which can occur.
这个主要由每天轮流运转
This consists mainly of running the boiler...
酒店不同部分的供暖锅炉组成
...heating different parts of the hotel on a daily rotating basis...
当发生损坏的时候要修理
...repairing damage as it occurs...
及时修复  才能抵御恶劣的天气
...and doing repairs so the elements can't get a foothold.
听起来没什么难的
That sounds fine to me.
实际上  那不是件非常费尽的工作
Physically, it's not a very demanding job.
在冬季  在那儿唯一有点难受的事可能就是
The only thing that can get a bit trying here during the winter...
巨大的孤立感
...is a tremendous sense of isolation.
那正是我所寻找的
That just happens to be exactly what I'm looking for.
我正在构思一个新的写作计划
I'm outlining a new writing project.
我刚好想要安静地待5个月
Five months of peace is just what I want.
那儿不错  杰克
That's very good, Jack.
因为  对有些人来说
Because, for some people. . .
孤独
...solitude...
跟与世隔绝
...and isolation...
可能  自然而然地  会成为问题所在
...can, of itself, become a problem.
对我来说不是
Not for me.
那你太太跟儿子呢  你认为他们能忍受吗
How about your wife and son? Do you think they'll take to it?
他们会很喜欢那儿的
They'll love it.
很好
Great.
在将你移交给比尔之前
Before I turn you over to Bill...
我想还有另外一件事我们得谈谈
...there's one other thing I think we should talk about.
并不是耸人听闻
Not to sound melodramatic...
但那会令少许人
...but it's been known to give a few people
对那份工作重新思量
second thoughts about the job.
勾起我的好奇心了
I'm intrigued.
我不知道丹佛那边的人是不是说过
I don't suppose they said anything in Denver...
有关在1970年冬季时期我们这儿发生的悲剧
...about the tragedy we had up here during the winter of 1970.
没说过
I don't believe they did.
我这份工作的前任
My predecessor in this job...
雇了一位加查理斯·格雷迪的人来做冬季看门人
...hired a man named Charles Grady as the winter caretaker.
他带着他的妻子跟两个8岁和10岁的女儿
He came up with his wife and two little girls of about 8 and 1 0.
他有很好的雇佣纪律  推荐人
He had a good employment record, good references.
据我所知
And from what I've been told, he seemed...
他看起来完成是个正常人
...like a completely normal individual.
但在冬季期间的某天
But at some point during the winter...
他肯定遭受了某种事
...he must have suffered some kind
导致精神完全崩溃
of a complete mental breakdown.
他发狂了
He ran amuck...
并用斧子把他的家人都杀了
...and killed his family with an ax.
把他们的尸体整齐地堆放到西翼的一间房里
Stacked them neatly in a room in the west wing, and then...
然后吞枪自杀
...he put both barrels of his shotgun in his mouth.
警方认为
The police thought...
那就是老前辈们过去称之为的幽居病
...that it was what the old-timers used to call cabin fever.
当人们被长时间地关闭在一起的时候
A kind of claustrophobic reaction which can occur...
会发生的一种幽闭恐惧症反应
...when people are shut in together over long periods of time.
真是个离奇的故事
That is...quite a story.
是的
Yeah, it is.
我仍旧难以相信那事确实发生于此
It's still hard for me to believe it actually happened here.
但确实发生过
But it did.
我想你可以体会为何我想要告诉你此事
I think you can appreciate why I wanted to tell you about it.
当然
I certainly can.
我也明白为何你们在丹佛的工作人员
I also understand why your people in Denver
把它留给你来告诉我
left it for you to tell me.
显然  有些人会不愿待在
Obviously, some people can be put off
发生过这种事的地方
from staying in a place where something like that happened.
你可以放心  那不会发生在我的身上
You can rest assured that's not gonna happen with me.
据我太太所关心的
And as far as my wife is concerned...
当我告诉她的时候  我肯定她绝对会很感兴趣
I'm sure she'll be absolutely fascinated when I tell her.
她着迷于鬼怪故事
She's a confirmed ghost story
跟恐怖片
and horror film addict.
托尼  你觉得爸爸能得到那份工作吗
Tony, do you think dad'll get the job?
他已经受聘了
He already did.
他过会就会打电话告诉温迪了
He's gonna phone Wendy up in a few minutes to tell her.
喂
Hello.
-宝贝  -亲爱的  怎么了
- Hi, babe. - Hi, Hon. How's it going?
很好  我在酒店还有很多事要讨论
Great. I'm at the hotel and I still have a lot to go through.
我想9点或者10点之前可能回不去了
I don't think I can get home before 9 or 1 0.
听起来你好像得到那份工作了
Sounds like you got the job.
是的  地方很漂亮
Right. It's a beautiful place.
你跟丹尼会很喜欢的
You and Danny are gonna love it.
托尼  你干吗不想去酒店啊
Tony, why don't you wanna go to the hotel?
不知道
I don't know.
你肯定知道  快点  告诉我吧
You do too know. Now come on, tell me.
我不想说
I don't want to.
拜托
Please.
不要
No.
托尼  快告诉我
Now, Tony, tell me.
停业日
我们肯定处于高地了  空气感觉都不一样了
Boy, we must really be high up. The air feels so different.
-爸爸  -怎么了
- Dad? - Yes?
我饿了
I'm hungry.
谁叫你不吃早餐的
Well, you should've eaten your breakfast.
我们一到酒店就弄东西给你吃
We'll get you something as soon as we get to the hotel.
好吧  妈妈
Okay, Mom.
这儿不是多纳小队成为雪中亡魂的地方吗
Wasn't it around here that the Donner party got snowbound?
80年代一批西移的加利福尼亚移民
我想那是西边  在内华达山丘
I think that was Farther West, in the Sierras.
什么是多纳小队
What was the Donner party?
他们是有蓬大马车时期的一个移民小队
They were a party of settlers in covered-wagon times.
在某个冬天的山丘里  他们被雪困住了
They got snowbound one winter in the mountains.
为了活下去不得不同类相食
They had to resort to cannibalism in order to stay alive.
你是说他们把对方吃了
You mean they ate each other up?
为了活下来  他们不得不那么做
They had to in order to survive.
杰克
Jack.
别担心  妈妈
Don't worry, Mom.
我知道有关同类相食的事  我在电视上看过
I know all about cannibalism. I saw it on TV.
瞧  没关系的
See, it's okay.
他在电视上看过
He saw it on the television.
-飞机什么时候起飞  -8点半
- What time does the plane leave? - 8:30.
我们还有很多时间来检查一切
That gives us plenty of time to go over everything.
-再见  厄尔曼先生  -再见
- Goodbye, Mr. Ullman. - Bye.
早上好  希望没让你等很久
Good morning. I hope you haven't been waiting too long.
没关系  我们刚好有时间吃点东西
No problem. We had time to grab a bite to eat.
很好  在厨房关闭之前  你们刚好赶上
Good. Glad you made it before they shut down the kitchen.
你的家人看过周边环境了吗
Is your family having a look around?
还没  我儿子发现了游戏房
No, my son's discovered the games room.
-你们的行李都拿进来了吗  -在那儿呢
- Has your luggage been brought in? - Right there.
由于今天我们的人员都得清空
In view of all we have to cover today
我建议我们来快速参观一下你们的房间
I suggest we have a quick look
马上开始吧
at your apartment and get started right away.
把托伦斯的东西都拿到他们房间去
Have the Torrances' things brought to their apartment.
-好的  -我最好先去叫我的家人
- Fine. - I'd better collect my family first.
这是我们的科罗拉多休息室
This is our Colorado Lounge.
好漂亮啊
It's beautiful.
天哪
My god!
这地方太漂亮了  不是吗  亲爱的
This place is fantastic, isn't it, Hon?
当然
It sure is.
这里是酒店的员工宿舍
This is the staff wing of the hotel.
在冬季其它任何房间都不供暖
None of the other bedrooms are heated during the winter.
-再见  厄尔曼先生  -再见  妞儿们
- Goodbye, Mr. Ullman. - Goodbye, girls.
这里是你们的寓所
And here are your quarters.
客厅  卧室  浴室
Living room, bedroom, bathroom.
还有一间让你们的儿子住的卧房
And a small bedroom for your son.
很适合小孩子住
Perfect for a child.
那幢观景酒店什么时候建造的
When was the overlook built?
1907年开始建造
Construction started in 1907.
1909年竣工的
It was finished in 1909.
地点本来选在一个印第安人的坟场
The site's supposed to be on an Indian burial ground.
实际上当他们建造的时候
They actually had to repel...
不得不抵制些许印地安人的袭击
...a few Indian attacks as they were building it.
那辆是我们的雪猫车
That's our snowcat.
你们俩都会开车吗
Can you both drive a car?
那就好  基本上驾驶雪猫车跟开汽车差不多
That's fine. Basically the snowcat operates very much like a car.
不需要很长时间驾驭
Won't take long to get the hang of it.
这是厨房吧
This is the kitchen, huh?
是的  就是厨房
Yeah, this is it.
你觉得如何啊  丹尼  够大吧
How do you like it, Danny? Is it big enough for you?
够大  是我所见过的最大的地方
Yeah. It's the biggest place I ever seen.
这里整个地方就像个巨大的迷宫
Yeah, this whole place is such an enormous maze.
我觉得每次我进来  得在后面留下面包屑作为记号才行
I feel like I'll have to leave a trail of breadcrumbs every time I come in.
别让它把你吓倒了
Don't let it get you down.
地方是很大  但仍旧只是个厨房而已
It's big, but it still ain't nothing but a kitchen.
这儿的很多东西你永远都不会碰
A lot of this stuff you'll never have to touch.
即使要做我都不知道该怎么做呢
I wouldn't know what to do with it if I did.
有一件事是可以肯定的  就是你不用担心食物
One thing for sure, you don't have to worry about food.
就算你们在这儿吃一年
You folks could eat here for a year
菜单都不会重样
and never have the same menu twice.
这边是我们的小型冷藏间
Now, right here is our walk-in freezer.
这里是我们冷藏所有肉类的地方
This is where we keep all of our meat.
15根烤排骨
You got 15 rib roasts...
30包10磅重的汉堡包
30 ten-pound bags of hamburger.
12只火鸡  大约40只鸡
We got 12 turkeys, about 40 chickens...
50份牛腰肉  2打烤猪排
50 sirloin steaks, two dozen of pork roast...
还有20只羊腿  你喜欢吃羊肉吗  道格
and 20 legs of lamb. Do you like lamb, Doc?
不喜欢 不喜欢  那你最喜欢的食物是什么
No. You don't? What's your favorite food, then?
炸薯条跟番茄酱
French fries and ketchup.
我想我们也可以搞定  道格
I think we can manage that too, Doc.
出去吧  小心台阶
Come along, now. Watch your step.
你怎么知道我们叫他道格
How'd you know we call him Doc?
不好意思  你说什么
Beg your pardon?
道格  你两次叫丹尼都叫"道格"
Doc. You called Danny ''Doc'' twice.
-是吗  -是的
- I did? - Yeah.
我们有时也叫他道格  就像兔八哥动画片里的
We call him Doc sometimes, like in the Bugs Bunny cartoons.
但你是怎么知道的
But how did you know?
我猜想我可能听你那么叫过他吧
I guess I probably heard you call him that.
有可能  但我实在不记得
It's possible. But I honestly don't remember...
在我们跟你一起的时候有这么叫过
calling him that since we've been with you.
不管怎么说  他长得很像道格  不是吗
Anyway, he looks like a Doc, doesn't he?
怎么了  道格
What's up, Doc?
这里是贮藏室
Now, this is the storeroom.
这里我们用来
In here is where we keep...
储藏所有干货跟罐头食品
all the dried goods and the canned goods.
我们有水果罐头跟蔬菜罐头
We got canned fruits and vegetables. . .
鱼肉类罐头  冷热谷类食品
canned fish and meats, hot and cold cereals.
波士特土司  玉米片  糖小麦
Post toasties, corn flakes, sugar puffs...
波士特土司  美国一个谷类品牌早餐
爆米花  燕麦片  麦制的奶油
rice krispies, oatmeal, wheatena and cream of wheat.
一打罐装的黑糖蜜
You got a dozen jugs of black molasses.
60盒奶粉
We got 60 boxes of dried milk...
来点冰淇淋怎么样  道格
How'd you like some ice cream, Doc?
手卷
Sociables, finger rolls...
还有7种不同种类的
and 7 kinds of what have you.
我们有桃脯  杏干
Now, we've got dried peaches, dried apricots...
葡萄干跟西梅干
dried raisins and dried prunes.
如果你喜欢的话  可以换着口味吃
You know, you gotta keep regular if you wanna be happy.
-处得怎么样啊  -很好
- How're you getting on? - Just fine.
我们可以借用一下托伦斯太太吗
Can we borrow Mrs. Torrance for a few minutes?
我们要去地下室看看
We're on our way to the basement.
我保证我们不会去很久的
I promise we won't keep her very long.
没问题  厄尔曼先生  我刚好要去拿冰淇淋
No problem, Mr. Ullman. I was just getting to the ice cream.
你喜欢吃冰淇淋吗  道格
You like ice cream, Doc?
-喜欢  -我想你会喜欢
- Yeah. - I thought you did.
在等你们回来的时候  介意我给丹尼吃冰淇淋吗
You folks mind if I give Danny some ice cream while we wait?
-不介意  -我们不介意
- Not at all. - We don't mind.
-很好  -你可以吗  道格
- Good. - Sound good to you, Doc?
-可以  -好的  乖点噢
- Yeah. - Okay, you behave yourself.
-你喜欢吃什么口味的冰淇淋  -巧克力的
- What kind of ice cream do you like? - Chocolate.
巧克力冰淇淋  走吧  孩子
Chocolate it shall be. Come on, son.
今天所有的活动都太神奇了
It's amazing, all this activity today.
客人跟一些员工昨天就离开了
The guests and some staff left yesterday, but the...
但最后一天总会比较忙
last day's always hectic.
大家都想尽快启程
Everybody wants to be on their way as early as possible.
今晚5点的时候  这儿就一个人也没有了
By 5:00 tonight, you'll never know anybody was ever here.
-就像一艘幽灵船  -是的
- Just like a ghost ship, huh? - Yes.
你知道我是怎么知道你叫道格的吗
Do you know how I knew your name was Doc?
你知道我在说什么  对吧
You know what I'm talking about, don't you?
我记得当我还是小孩的时候
I can remember when I was a little boy...
我祖母跟我可以在完全不开口的
my grandmother and I could hold conversations...
情况下交谈
entirely without ever opening our mouths.
她称之为"闪灵"
She called it "shining".
很长一段时间  我以为只有我们俩
And for a long time I thought it was just the two of us...
有"闪灵"的本领
that had "the shine" to us.
就像你可能认为你是唯一拥有那项本领的人
Just like you probably thought you was the only one.
但有其他的人
But there are other folks...
然而他们大部分都不知道  或是不相信
though mostly they don't know it, or don't believe it.
你拥有这项本领多久了
How long have you been able to do it?
你为何不想说
Why don't you wanna talk about it?
我不应该说
I'm not supposed to.
谁说你不该说的
Who says you ain't supposed to?
托尼
Tony.
谁是托尼
Who's Tony?
托尼是寄居于我口中的小男孩
Tony's the little boy that lives in my mouth.
托尼就是那个告诉你事情的人吗
Is Tony the one that...tells you things?
是的
Yes.
他怎么告诉你呢
How does he tell you things?
就像我去睡觉  然后他会告诉我事情
It's like I go to sleep, and he shows me things.
但当我醒来的时候  我无法记起一切事情
But when I wake up, I can't remember everything.
你爸妈知道有关托尼的事吗
Does your Mom and Dad know about Tony?
知道
Yes.
他们知道他告诉你事情吗
Do they know he tells you things?
不知道  托尼让我永远不要告诉他们
No. Tony told me never to tell them.
托尼曾告诉过你任何有关这个地方的事吗
Has Tony ever told you anything about this place?
有关观景酒店的事
About the overlook hotel?
我不知道
I don't know.
认真想想  道格  想想
Now think real hard, Doc. Think.
这儿有什么不好的事吗
Is there something bad here?
道格  当什么事发生的时候
You know, Doc, when something happens...
是有迹可寻的
it can leave a trace of itself behind.
像是
Say, like...
如果某人把面包烤焦了
if someone burns toast.
也许发生的事会在后面留下其它痕迹
Maybe things that happen leave other kind of traces behind.
不是任何人都会注意到的事情
Not things that anyone can notice.
但拥有闪灵能力的人可以看到
But things that people who shine can see.
就像他们可以预见未来一样
Just like they can see things that haven't happened yet...
有时他们可以看到很久以前发生的事
sometimes they can see things that happened a long time ago.
我觉得多年来在这间特别的酒店里
I think a lot of things happened right here...
发生过很多事情
in this particular hotel over the years.
并且不是所有事情都是好事
And not all of them was good.
237号房间呢
What about room 237?
237号房间
Room 237?
你害怕237号房间  是吗
You're scared of room 237, ain't you?
不  我不怕
No,I ain't.
哈罗伦先生  237号房间有什么东西吗
Mr. Hallorann, what is in room 237?
什么也没有
Nothing.
在237号房里没有什么
There ain't nothing in room 237.
但不管怎样  没事你别往里面跑
But you ain't got no business going in there anyway.
离那儿远点
So stay out.
明白吗  离那儿远点
You understand? Stay out!
一个月后
早安  亲爱的
Good morning, Hon.
你的早餐做好喽
Your breakfast is ready.
几点了
What time is it?
将近11点半了
It's about 11:30.
11点半了  天哪
11:30? Jesus.
我猜想我们昨晚太晚睡了
I guess we've been staying up too late.
我知道
I know it.
我按你的喜好做的  太阳蛋
I made them just the way you like them, sunny-side up.
太好了
Nice.
外面真的很漂亮
It's really pretty outside.
等你吃完早餐后  带我出去走走怎么样
How about taking me for a walk after you finish your breakfast?
我本该先写作
I suppose I ought to try to do some writing first.
有灵感吗
Any ideas yet?
很多灵感
Lots of ideas.
就是没一个好的
No good ones.
灵感会来的
Well, something'll come.
习惯每天进入写作状态就行了
It's just a matter of settling into the habit of writing every day.
对  进入状态就好了
Yeah. That's all it is.
-好的  -你跑不赢我的
- All right. - And you're gonna lose.
我会追上你的  你最好跑快点
And I'm gonna get you. You'd better run fast!
小心
Look out!
要追上喽
I'm coming in close.
输的人做家务
Loser has to keep America clean.
做家务
Keep America clean.
丹尼  你赢了
Danny, you win.
我们慢慢走休息一下吧
Let's take the rest of this walking.
好的
Okay.
拉着我的手
Give me your hand.
-漂亮吗  -漂亮
- Isn't it beautiful? - Yeah.
死胡同
Dead end.
我们走出来了
We made it.
-漂亮吗  -漂亮
- Isn't it beautiful? - Yeah.
-太漂亮了  -是的
- It's so pretty. - Yeah.
我觉得这里也不是很大嘛  你觉得呢
I didn't think it was gonna be this big. Did you?
不大
No.
星期二
亲爱的
Hi, Hon.
写得怎么样了
How's it going?
还好
Fine.
今天写了很多吗
Get a lot written today?
是的
Yes.
天气预报说今晚会下雪
Hey, the weather forecast said it's gonna snow tonight.
你想要我干吗
What do you want me to do about it?
别这样  亲爱的
Come on, Hon.
脾气别这么臭啊
Don't be so grouchy.
我不是
I'm not...
脾气臭
being grouchy.
我只是想完成我的工作而已
I just wanna finish my work.
好的  我明白了
Okay. I understand.
我待会儿会拿几份三明治过来
I'll come back later with a couple of sandwiches.
也许你会让我拜读你的大作
Maybe you'll let me read something then.
温迪
Wendy...
让我来跟你解释一下吧
let me explain something to you.
当你进来打断我的时候  你会令我分散注意力的
When you come in and interrupt, you're breaking my concentration.
你分散我的注意力
You're distracting me...
然后我就要花时间重新回到那个状态
and it will then take me time to get back to where I was.
明白吗
Understand?
-明白了  -很好
- Yeah. - Fine.
我们现在定几条规矩吧
We're going to make a new rule:
不管什么时候我在这里
Whenever I'm in here...
你听到我在打字
and you hear me typing...
或是不管你他妈的听到我在这里干什么
or whatever the fuck you hear me doing in here...
当我在这儿的时候  就表示我在工作
when I'm in here, that means I am working.
表示你不能进来
That means don't come in.
你觉得你能做到吗
Now, do you think you can handle that?
能
Yeah.
很好
Fine.
你何不现在就开始行动呢  他妈的给我滚出去
Why don't you start right now and get the fuck out of here?
好
Okay.
没打中
Missed!
Don't have!
我可不再让你喽
No fair anymore.
星期六
知道啦
I knew it.
这里是KDK12呼叫KDK1
This is KDK 12 calling KDK 1 .
KDK12呼叫KDK1
KDK 12 to KDK 1.
这里是KDK1  我们收到了  完毕
This is KDK 1 . We're receiving you. Over.
你好  我是住在观景酒店的温迪·托伦斯
Hi, this is Wendy Torrance at the Overlook hotel.
你好  你们在上面住的怎么样啊  完毕
Hi, how are you folks getting on up there? Over.
还不错
We're just fine.
但我们的电话接收不大好
But our telephones aren't doing too well.
可能是线路坏了吗  完毕
Are the lines down, by any chance? Over.
是的  由于暴风雪好几条线路都坏了  完毕
Yes, quite a few of them are down due to the storm. Over.
有可能很快修好吗  完毕
Any chance of them being repaired soon? Over.
我也说不好
I wouldn't like to say.
大多数情况到春天才会派人修复  完毕
Most winters they stay that way until spring. Over.
这场暴风雪破坏力还真大  是吧  完毕
Boy, this storm is really something, isn't it? Over.
是的  这是近年来最大的暴风雪
Yes. It's one of the worst we've had for years.
还有什么事我们可以为您效劳的吗  托伦斯太太  完毕
Is there anything else we can do for you, Mrs. Torrance? Over.
没有了  完毕
I suppose not. Over.
如果你们在上面有任何问题  就打给我们
If you folks have any problems up there, just give us a call.
还有  托伦斯太太
And, Mrs. Torrance?
如果你一直开着广播  也许会是个好注意  完毕
It might be a good idea if you leave your radio on all the time. Over.
好的  我们会开着的
Okay. We'll do that.
很高兴跟你谈话
It was real nice talking to you.
再见  完毕  挂了
Bye. Over and out.
你好  丹尼
Hello, Danny.
来跟我们玩吧
Come and play with us.
来跟我们玩吧  丹尼
Come and play with us, Danny.
永远
Forever...
and ever...
永远
and ever.
托尼
Tony...
我怕
I'm scared.
记得哈罗伦先生说的
Remember what Mr. Hallorann said.
就像书中的图片一样  丹尼
It's just like pictures in a book, Danny.
不是真的
It isn't real.
星期一
我可以去我的房间拿消防车吗
Can I go to my room and get my fire engine?
先过来这边待一会儿
Come here for a minute first.
过得怎么样  道格
How's it going, Doc?
还好
Okay.
玩得开心吗
Having a good time?
开心  爸爸
Yes, Dad.
很好
Good.
我希望你玩得开心
I want you to have a good time.
我很开心  爸爸
I am, Dad.
-爸爸  -什么事
- Dad? - Yes?
你感觉很糟吗
Do you feel bad?
没有
No.
我只是有点累而已
I'm just a little bit tired.
那你为什么不去睡觉呢
Then why don't you go to sleep?
我不能睡
I can't.
我还有很多事要做
I got too much to do.
爸爸
Dad?
什么事
Yes?
你喜欢这间酒店吗
Do you like this hotel?
喜欢
Yeah. I do.
我很喜欢它
I love it.
你呢
Don't you?
喜欢吧
I guess so.
很好
Good.
我希望你喜欢这儿
I want you to like it here.
我希望我们能永远待在这儿
I wish we could stay here forever...
永远
and ever...
and ever.
爸爸
Dad?
什么
What?
你绝不会伤害妈妈或是我的吧
You would never hurt Mommy or me, would you?
什么意思
What do you mean?
你妈妈曾那么跟你说的吗
Did your mother ever say that to you?
说我会伤害你们
That I would hurt you?
没有  爸爸
No, Dad.
你确定
You sure?
确定  爸爸
Yes, Dad.
我爱你  丹尼
I love you, Danny.
我爱你胜过于
I love you more than anything else...
世界上的任何东西
in the whole world...
我绝不会做任何伤害你的事
and I would never do anything to hurt you.
永远不会
Never.
你知道的  对吧
You know that, don't you?
知道  爸爸
Yes, Dad.
很好
Good.
星期三
妈妈
Mom?
妈妈  你在里面吗
Mom, are you in there?
杰克
Jack!
发生什么事了
What happened?
亲爱的
Honey...
怎么了
What's wrong?
我做了一个有史以来
I had the most...
最可怕的噩梦
terrible nightmare I ever had.
-最可怕的梦  -没事了
- It was the most horrible dream. - It's okay, it's okay now.
真的
Really.
我梦到
I dreamed that I...
我杀了你跟丹尼
that I killed you and Danny.
但不只是杀死你们而已
But I didn't just kill you.
我还把你们剁成一小块一小块
I cut you up into little pieces.
天哪
My God.
我肯定是发疯了
I must be losing my mind.
一切都会好起来的
Everything's gonna be all right.
快点  快起来
Come on. Let's get up off the floor.
没事了  坐好
It's okay. There. Now, sit up.
没事了
It's okay.
丹尼
Danny!
一切都安好
Everything's okay!
去你自己的房间玩会
Just go play in your room for a while.
你爸爸只是有点头痛而已
Your Dad's just got a headache.
丹尼  听我的话  去你自己房间玩
Danny, mind what I say. Go play in your room.
亲爱的  我先去叫他出去
Honey, let me just go get him out of here.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
你干吗不听我的话
Why don't you mind me?
天哪
Oh, my God.
你的脖子怎么了
What happened to your neck?
你把他弄伤的
You did this to him...
是吗
...didn't you?!
你个狗娘养的
You son of a bitch!
你把他弄伤的
You did this to him!
是吗
Didn't you?!
你怎么做得出来
How could you?!
天哪  我可以为了一杯酒付出任何代价
God! I'd give anything for a drink.
就为喝一杯啤酒
I'd give my goddamn soul...
我可以付出该死的灵魂
for just a glass of beer.
你好  劳埃德
Hi, Lloyd.
今晚生意有点惨淡啊  是吧
A little slow tonight, isn't it?
是的  托伦斯先生
Yes it is, Mr. Torrance.
要喝点什么
What'll it be?
很高兴你那么问我  劳埃德
I'm awfully glad you asked me that, Lloyd...
因为我的钱包里
because I just happen to have two twenties...
刚好有两张20块跟两张10块
and two tens right here in my wallet.
我怕它们要直到4月份才能花出去
I was afraid they were gonna be there until next April.
那么 这样吧
So here's what:
给我开一瓶波旁威士忌
You slip me a bottle of Bourbon...
倒一小杯  加些冰块
a little glass and some ice.
可以吧  劳埃德
You can do that, can't you, Lloyd?
你不是很忙  是吧
You're not too busy, are you?
是的  先生  我一点都不忙
No, sir. I'm not busy at all.
真是个好人
Good man.
你准备好给我倒酒
You set them up...
我会一杯接着一杯得开怀畅饮
and I'll knock them back, one by one.
白人男子的重负啊  劳埃德  老兄
White man's burden, Lloyd, my man.
白人男子的重负啊
White man's burden.
劳埃德
Say, Lloyd...
貌似我没带够钱
it seems I'm temporarily light.
我可以赊账吗
How's my credit in this joint, anyway?
可以  托伦斯先生
Your credit's fine, Mr. Torrance.
太好了
That's swell.
我喜欢你  劳埃德
I like you,Lloyd.
我一直都喜欢你
I always liked you.
你一直是他们之中最好的人
You were always the best of them.
这方面上  你是从廷巴克图到波特兰  到缅因州
Best goddamned bartender...
或是波特兰  俄勒冈州
from Timbuktu to Portland, Maine.
该死的最好的酒吧间男招待
Or Portland, Oregon, for that matter.
谢谢你的夸奖
Thank you for saying so.
我绝不会对他动手  该死的
I never laid a hand on him, goddamn it.
我没有
I didn't.
我不会动他一根汗毛
I wouldn't touch one hair on his goddamn little head.
我爱那个狗娘养的
I love the little son of a bitch.
我可以为他做任何事
I'd do anything for him.
为他做该死的任何事
Any fucking thing for him.
但那个婊子
But that bitch!
只要我还活着
As long as I live...
她永远不会让我忘记所发生的事
she'll never let me forget what happened.
我确实伤害过他一次  行了吧
I did hurt him once, okay?
那只是个意外
It was an accident.
完全是无心的
Completely unintentional.
任何人都有可能发生
It could have happened to anybody.
那是该死的3年前发生的事
And it was three goddamn years ago!
那个小操蛋的把我所有的文章扔得满地都是
The little fucker had thrown all my papers all over the floor.
我所做的只是想让他停下来
All I tried to do was pull him up.
一时用力过猛
A momentary loss of muscular coordination.
我是说
I mean...
只是稍微用了点劲
a few extra foot-pounds of energy...
一点点  一点点劲
per second. Per second.
谢天谢地你在这儿
Thank god you're here.
酒店里还有其他人
There's someone else in the hotel with us.
有个疯女人在其中一个房间里面
There's a crazy woman in one of the rooms.
她想要掐死丹尼
She tried to strangle Danny.
你他妈的疯了吗
Are you out of your fucking mind?
没有  是真的  真的  我发誓  丹尼告诉我的
No. It's the truth. Really, I swear it! Danny told me.
他进到其中一个卧室
He went up into one of the bedrooms.
门开着  他看到这个疯女人在浴缸里面
The door was open, and he saw this crazy woman in the bathtub.
她想要掐死他
She tried to strangle him!
哪个房间
Which room was it?
这里是由格兰·芮恩克和安·比什伯
From channel 10 in Miami...
所主持的拥有一只备受赞誉的新闻团队的
...this is newswatch with Glen Rinker...
迈阿密第十频道
...Ann Bishop, and the award-winning newswatch team.
晚上好  我是格兰·芮恩克  第10频道新闻看看看
Good evening. I'm Glen Rinker, Newswatch ten.
当迈阿密持续90年代有史以来的
As Miami continues to swelter in a record winter heat wave...
冬季高温酷暑天气的时候
...bringing temperatures to the 90s...
中央以及几个州的山脉已经被积雪覆盖
...central and mountain states are buried in snow.
在科罗拉多州  今晚几个小时内就降了10英寸厚的雪
In Colorado, 10 inches of snow fell in just a few hours tonight.
要去洛基山旅行根本不可能
Travel in the Rockies is almost impossible.
机场被关闭了  数千名乘客滞留机场
Airports are shut down, stranding thousands of passengers.
高速公路被积雪封死
Highways are blocked by snowdrifts.
铁轨上面有结冰
Railroad tracks are frozen.
科罗拉多州官员告诉新闻看看看记者
Officials in Colorado tell Newswatch...
至少3人被寒风冻死
...at least 3 have been killed by exposure to freezing winds.
科罗拉多州州长预计将
The governor of Colorado is expected...
宣布气象预警
...to declare a weather emergency.
国民警卫队可能被调来
The national guard might be called out...
清理道路积雪
...to clear roads.
气象预报  今晚跟明天
Forecasters predict more snow...
将会有强降雪跟强风来袭
...and heavy winds tonight and tomorrow...
气温将降到0度以下
...with temperatures dropping well below zero.
现在来播报一下佛罗里达州  情况刚好相反
Back here in Florida, we've got the opposite problem.
持续高温湿热天气
The heat and humidity are supposed to climb.
当地海滩人潮涌动
Local beaches should be jammed.
我们的气象专家  沃尔特·柯罗尼斯
Our weather expert, Walter Cronice...
将会在新闻看看看播报当地气象
...will have the local forecast later on Newswatch.
抱歉  您所拨打的电话暂时无法接通
We're sorry. Your call cannot be completed as dialed.
如果您需要帮助的话  请打给电话接线员
If you need assistance, please call the operator.
杰克吗
Jack?
是  是我
Yes, it's me.
谢天谢地
Thank God.
有发现什么吗
Did you find anything?
没有  什么都没有
No. Nothing at all.
我根本没看到什么东西
I didn't see one goddamn thing.
你有进丹尼说的那个房间吗  237号房
You went into the room Danny said? To 237?
是的  进去了
Yes, I did.
那你什么也没看到吗
And you didn't see anything at all?
绝对没有
Absolutely nothing.
他怎么样了
How is he?
他还在睡觉
He's still asleep.
那就好
Good.
我肯定明早他就会没事了
I'm sure he'll be himself again in the morning.
你确定没进错房间吗
Are you sure it was the right room?
我是说  也许丹尼搞错了
I mean, maybe Danny made a mistake.
他肯定进去过那个房间
He must have gone in that room.
门开着  灯也开着
The door was open, the lights were on.
我就是不明白
I just don't understand it.
他脖子上的那些伤痕是怎么回事
What about those bruises on his neck?
有人弄的
Somebody did that to him.
我觉得
I think...
是他自己弄的
...he did it to himself.
不
No.
不可能
That's not possible.
当局者迷
Once you rule out his version of what happened...
旁观者清
...there is no other explanation.
是吗
Is there?
不管事实是什么
Whatever the explanation is...
我觉得
...I think we... ...
我们得带丹尼离开这儿
have to get Danny out of here.
带他离开这儿
Get him out of here?
你是说
You mean...
离开这个酒店吗
...just leave the hotel?
当我终于有机会完成某件事的时候
It is so fucking... ...typical of you to create a problem like this...
你他妈的就专门给我制造这样的问题
...when I finally have a chance to accomplish something!
当我真正专注于我的事业的时候
When I'm really into my work!
如果我现在回去
I could really write my own ticket
就能真正自行决定了吗
if I went back now, couldn't I?
当个民工  在洗车场工作
Shoveling out driveways, working in a car wash.
有你喜欢的工作吗
Any of that appeal to you?
我纵容你毁灭我的生活就到此为止
I have let you fuck up my life so far...
这次我不会再让你搞砸我的生活了
...but I am not going to let you fuck this up.
-晚上好  这里是林业局  -你好
- Good evening. Forest service. - Hello.
我是迪克·哈罗伦
My name is Dick Hallorann.
我是观景酒店的主厨
I'm the head chef at the Overlook Hotel.
晚上好  我能为你做些什么吗
Good evening. What can I do for you?
我曾试着紧急呼叫酒店电话
I've been trying to make an urgent phone call up there...
但接线员说电话线坏了
...but the operator said the phone lines are down.
由于暴风雪的缘故  这儿附近的很多线路都坏了
A lot of lines around here are down due to the storm.
我也不愿劳烦您
I hate to put you through any trouble...
但那里有一家人住在酒店
...but there's a family up there all by themselves
并带着一个小孩
with a young kid.
由于这场暴风雪等等其它因素
And with this storm and everything...
你最好能通过广播呼叫他们  看看他们是否一切安好
...I'd appreciate it if you'd give them a call on your radio...
我将万分感激
...just to see if everything's okay.
很乐意为您效劳
I'll be glad to do that.
您要不过20分钟左右再打过来吧
Why don't you call me back in about 20 minutes?
非常感谢  我会的
Thank you very much. I'll do that.
好的  先生
All right, sir.
晚上好  托伦斯先生
Good evening, Mr. Torrance.
晚上好
Good evening.
你好  劳埃德
Hi, Lloyd.
离开了  但现在我又回来了
Been away, but now I'm back.
晚上好  托伦斯先生
Good evening, Mr. Torrance.
很高兴见到你
It's good to see you.
回来的感觉真好  劳埃德
It's good to be back, Lloyd.
要喝点什么  先生
What'll it be, sir?
给我来杯解宿醉的酒吧
Hair of the dog that bit me.
加冰波旁威士忌
Bourbon on the rocks.
就它了
That'll do her.
免费的  托伦斯先生
No charge to you, Mr. Torrance.
免费的
No charge?
在这儿你不用付钱
Your money's no good here.
酒店请客
Orders from the house.
痛快地喝吧  托伦斯先生
Drink up, Mr. Torrance.
谁请我喝酒啊
I'm the kind of man likes to know who's buying their drinks.
那不是你所要关心的问题  托伦斯先生
It's not a matter that concerns you, Mr. Torrance.
至少这个你不用担心
At least not at this point.
你说了算  劳埃德
Anything you say, Lloyd.
你说了算
Anything you say.
天哪  非常抱歉  先生
Oh, dear! I'm so sorry, sir.
天哪
Oh, dear. Oh, dear.
我把你的外套弄脏了  先生
I've made an awful mess of your jacket, sir.
没关系  我有很多外套
That's all right. I've got plenty of jackets.
我怕是荷兰产蛋酒  先生  容易造成衣服褪色
I'm afraid it's advocaat, sir. It tends to stain.
荷兰产蛋酒  是吗
Advocaat, is it? Yes, sir.
是的  先生  我想最好
I think the best thing...
去洗手间
...is to come along to the gentlemen's room...
我们用水把它弄掉  先生
...and we'll get some water to it, sir.
看来你身上也溅到了
Looks like you got a spot of it on yourself...
老吉夫斯
...Jeevesy old boy.
对理想男仆的尊称
没关系  你比较重要
That doesn't matter. You're the important one.
不敢当
Awfully nice of you to say.
当然  在污渍渗透到里面之前
Of course, I intended to change my jacket...
我打算换件外套
...before the fish and goose soiree.
明智之举啊
Very wise, sir. Very wise.
我帮你
I'll just...
把开挡住  吉夫斯
...hold this for you there, Jeevesy.
谢谢  先生  谢谢
Thank you, sir. Thank you.
看看我们用水能否把这个擦掉
Let's see if we can improve this with a little water.
好的  我就把  我的波旁威士忌跟荷兰产蛋酒放在那儿
All right. I'll just... ...set my bourbon and advocaat down right there.
不会耽误您很长时间
Won't keep you a moment.
好的
Fine.
-在这儿他们怎么称呼你  -叫我格雷迪  先生
- What do they call you around here?  - Grady, sir.
德尔伯特·格雷迪
Delbert Grady.
格雷迪
Grady?
是的  先生
Yes, sir.
-德尔伯特·格雷迪  -是的  先生
- Delbert Grady.  - That's right, sir.
格雷迪先生
Mr. Grady...
以前我是否在哪儿见过你
...haven't I seen you somewhere before?
何以见得  没见过  先生  我不相信我们曾见过
Why, no, sir. I don't believe so.
快弄干净了  先生
It's coming off now, sir.
格雷迪先生
Mr. Grady...
你曾经是这儿的守门人吗
...weren't you once the caretaker here?
何以见得  不是  先生  我不认为是
Why, no, sir. I don't believe so.
你结婚了  是吗  格雷迪先生
You a married man, are you, Mr. Grady?
是的  先生  我有个妻子跟两个女儿
Yes, sir. I have a wife and two daughters.
那
And...
-他们现在在哪儿  -这儿附近某个地方
- ...where are they now?  - They're somewhere around.
我不知道她们现在在哪儿
I'm not quite sure at the moment.
格雷迪先生
Mr. Grady?
你曾是这儿的守门人
You were the caretaker here.
我认识你
I recognize you.
我在报纸上看过你的照片
I saw your picture in the newspapers.
你
You...
把你的妻子跟女儿剁成一小块一小块
...chopped your wife and daughter up into little bits.
然后  你吞枪自杀
And... ...then you blew your brains out.
那太奇怪了  先生
That's strange, sir.
我一点印象都没有
I don't have any recollection of that at all.
格雷迪先生
Mr. Grady...
你曾是这儿的守门人
...you were the caretaker here.
对不起  我不同意你所说的  先生
I'm sorry to differ with you, sir.
但你
But you...
你才是守门人
...are the caretaker.
你一直是守门人
You've always been the caretaker.
我早该知道  先生
I should know, sir.
我一直在这儿
I've always been here.
你知道吗  托伦斯先生
Did you know, Mr. Torrance...
你儿子
...that your son...
试图带一个外人
...is attempting to bring an outside party...
加入这个工作
...into this situation?
你知道吗
Did you know that?
不知道
No.
他是 托伦斯先生
He is, Mr. Torrance.
谁
Who?
一个黑鬼
A nigger.
指那个酒店的主厨迪克·哈罗伦
一个黑鬼
A nigger?
那个黑鬼厨师
A nigger cook.
怎么做
How?
你儿子
Your son...
有超乎寻常的天赋
...has a very great talent.
我不觉得你知道有多么超乎寻常
I don't think you are aware how great it is.
但他试图用那个天赋
But he is attempting to use that talent...
来违背你的意愿
...against your will.
他是个非常任性的孩子
...he is a very willful boy.
他确实是个任性的孩子  托伦斯先生
Indeed he is, Mr. Torrance.
一个非常任性的孩子
A very willful boy.
一个相当
A rather... ...naughty boy...
调皮的孩子  我也许说得太明白了  先生
...if I may be so bold, sir.
是他的妈妈
It's his mother.
她  从中作梗
She... ...interferes.
也许需要好好
Perhaps they need a good...
责骂他们一顿
...talking-to.
如果
If
你不介意我那么说的话  也许
you don't mind my saying so... ...perhaps...
更严厉地斥责一番
...a bit more.
先生  我的孩子们  开始他们并不喜欢观景酒店
My girls, sir... ...they didn't care for the overlook at first.
实际上其中一个孩子还偷了一包火柴
One of them actually stole a pack of matches...
想要把酒店烧掉
...and tried to burn it down.
但我
But I...
纠正了她们的错误行为  先生
...corrected them, sir.
还有当我老婆想要阻止我执行我职责的时候
And when my wife tried to prevent me from doing my duty...
我
...I...
同样纠正了她的错误行为
...corrected her.
KDK1呼叫KDK12
KDK 1 calling kDK 12.
收到我的呼叫了吗
Are you receiving me?
KDK1呼叫KDK12
This is kDK 1 calling kDK 12.
KDK 1 calling kDK 12.
收到我的呼叫了吗
Do you read me?
KDK1呼叫KDK12
This is kDK 1 calling kDK 12.
KDK 1 calling kDK 12.
收到我的呼叫了吗
Are you receiving me?
您现在所收听的是由哈尔跟查理主持的丹佛在线节目
You're with Hal and Charlie on Khow, Denver.
外面的天气很恶劣
And we have a bad day out there.
丹佛市区大雪纷飞
Heavy snow throughout the Denver metro area.
许多山口  郎溪跟红山口已被封闭
Many mountain passes... ...wolf creek and red mountain passes are closed...
在艾森豪威尔隧道已经铺设了防滑链
...and the chain law is in effect at the Eisenhower tunnel.
我们从新闻部门获悉
We hear from the news department...
只有几架飞机将降落在斯特普尔顿机场
...only a few flights are landing at Stapleton airport...
像这么大的暴风雪
...and with storms like this...
我想整个机场将在一个小时内全部关机
...I guess the entire airport will be closed within the hour.
暴风雪将持续  气象观测组织
The storm will continue and the weather service...
已经向丹佛偏远市地区
...has declared a stockman 's and traveler's advisory...
宣布一个畜牧者跟旅行者公告
...for all areas outlying the Denver metro region.
杰克
Jack
只工作不玩耍  聪明的孩子也变傻
你觉得怎么样
How do you like it?
你在这儿干吗
What are you doing down here?
我只是
I just...
想要
...wanted...
跟你谈谈
...to talk to you.
好的
Okay.
那就谈谈吧
Let's talk.
你想要谈什么
What do you want to talk about?
我不记得了
I can't really remember.
你不记得了
You can't remember.
不
No...
我不记得了
...I can't.
也许是关于丹尼的事
Maybe it was about Danny?
也许是关于他的事
Maybe it was about him.
我认为我们该讨论一下丹尼的事
I think we should discuss Danny.
谋杀
我认为
I think...
我们该讨论一下该怎么处理他的事
...we should discuss what should be done with him.
该怎么处理他的事呢
What should be done with him?
我不知道
I don't know.
我可不认为你不知道
I don't think that's true.
我觉得你对该怎么处理丹尼的事
I think you have some very definite ideas...
有些非常明确的想法了
...about what should be done with Danny.
我想知道是什么想法
And I'd like to know what they are.
我
Well, I...
我认为也许该带他去看医生
...I think maybe he should be taken to a doctor.
你认为"也许"该带他去看医生
You think "maybe" he should be taken to a doctor?
你认为"也许"该什么时候带他去看医生呢
When do you think "maybe" he should be taken to a doctor?
尽快
As soon as possible?
"尽快吗"
"As soon as possible?"
杰克
Jack.
求你了
Please.
你认为他的健康也许亮了红灯
You believe his health might be at stake.
是的
Yes.
你关心他
And you are concerned about him.
那你关心我吗
And are you concerned about me?
-我当然关心你  -你当然关心我
- Of course I am.  - Of course you are!
你曾想过我的责任吗
Have you ever thought about my responsibilities?
你在说什么 你曾有过一刻
What are you talking about? Have you ever had a single moment's
想过我的责任吗
thought about my responsibilities?
你曾有一刻想过
Have you ever thought for a single moment...
我对我的雇主的职责所在吗
...about my responsibilities to my employers?
你曾有想起过
Has is ever occurred to you...
我同意照看酒店直到5月1号为止吗
...that I have agreed to look after the hotel until May 1 st?
酒店主人完全信任我  把酒店交由我看管
Does it matter to you at all...
还有我签署了同意书
...that the owners have placed their complete confidence in me...
表示接受上面所列的职责
...and that I have signed a letter of agreement...
对你来说重要吗
...in which I've accepted that responsibility?
你有一丁点什么是
Do you have the slightest idea...
道德跟伦理重要性的意识吗  有吗
...what a moral and ethical principal is? Do you?
你曾有想过如果我不履行我的职责
Has it ever occurred to you what would happen to my future...
我的将来将会怎么样吗
...if I fail to live up to my responsibilities?
你曾有想过吗  有吗
Has it ever occurred to you? Has it?
离我远点
Stay away from me!
为什么 我只想要回到我的房间去
Why? I just want to go back to my room.
为什么
Why?
我很纠结
Well...I'm very confused.
我需要时间好好想想
And I just need a chance to think things over.
你他妈的有一生的时间好好想
You've had your whole fucking life to think things over!
现在干点正经事去吧
What good's a few minutes more going to do you now?
离我远点 求你了
Stay away from me!
别伤害我
Please! Don't hurt me.
我不会伤害你的
I'm not going to hurt you.
-温迪  -离我远点
- Wendy.  - Stay away from me!
离我远点
Stay away!
亲爱的
Darling...
你心理就不能阳光一点吗
...light of my life.
我不会伤害你的
I'm not going to hurt you.
你不让我把话说完
You didn't let me finish my sentence.
我说过  "我不会伤害你的"
I said, "I'm not going to hurt you."
我只想让你脑袋清醒一点
I'm just going to bash your brains in.
我他妈的要把你的思想纠正过来
I'm going to bash them right the fuck in.
离我远点
Stay away from me!
我不会伤害你的
I'm not going to hurt you.
离我远点  离我远点
Stay away from me! Stay away!
求你了
Please!
别再挥球棒了
Stop swinging the bat.
离我远点
Stay away from me.
-温迪  把球棒放下  -别再靠近了
- Put that bat down, Wendy.  -Stop it!
-把球棒给我  -求你了
- Give me the bat.  - Please!
-离我远点  -把球棒给我
- Stay away! - Give me the bat.
-别再靠近了  -把球棒给我
- Stop it!  - Give me the bat.
-离我远点  -别再挥球棒了
- Stay away from me. - Stop swinging the bat.
别再靠近了
Please stop!
把球棒给我
Give me the bat.
求你  别再靠近了
Stay away from me.
-别再靠近了  -把球棒给我
- Stop it! - Give me the bat.
妈的
Goddamn...!
你要干吗
What are you doing?
等等
Wait a minute.
你要干吗
What are you doing?
等等
Wait a minute!
你要干吗
What are you doing?
快把门打开
Open the door!
妈的
Goddamn it!
快放我出去  妈的把门打开
Let me out of here! open the goddamn door!
温迪  听着
Wendy, listen.
快放我出去  我就当什么事也没发生过
Let me out and I'll forget the whole thing.
我就当什么事也没发生过
It'll be just like nothing ever happened.
宝贝
Baby...
我想你把我的头打伤了
...I think you hurt my head real bad.
我有点晕
I'm Dizzy.
我需要看医生
I need a doctor.
亲爱的
Honey...
别把我留在这儿
Don't leave me in here.
我要走了
I'm going to go now.
我今天就要开雪猫车带
I'm going to try...
丹尼去赛德纹德
...to get Danny down the Sidewinder in the snowcat today.
我会带位医生回来的
I'll bring back a doctor.
我要走了
I'm going to go now.
你会有个意外发现
You've got a big surprise coming to you.
你哪儿也甭想去
You're not going anywhere.
去检查一下雪猫车跟收音机
Go check out the snowcat and the radio,
你就会明白我所说的了
and you'll see what I mean.
去检查一下吧
Go check it out.
Go check it out!
去检查一下吧
Go check it out.
下午4点
是我  格雷迪  托伦斯先生
It's Grady, Mr. Torrance.
德尔伯特·格雷迪
Delbert Grady.
格雷迪
Grady?
你好  格雷迪
Hello, Grady.
托伦斯先生
Mr. Torrance...
我看你根本搞不定我们所讨论的事情
...I see you can hardly have taken care of the business we discussed.
别讽刺我了  格雷迪先生
No need to rub it in, Mr. Grady.
我一出去就会处理好那个事的
I'll deal with that situation as soon as I get out of here.
真的吗  托伦斯先生
Will you indeed, Mr. Torrance?
我想知道
I wonder.
我有我自己的疑虑
I have my doubts.
我  还有其他人  不得不认为
I, and others, have come to believe...
你并没有用心在办此事
...that your heart is not in this.
你没有勇气去做
That you haven't the belly for it.
再给我一次机会去证明  格雷迪先生
Just give me one more chance to prove it, Mr. Grady.
那就是我所要求的全部
That's all I ask.
托伦斯先生  你太太比我们想象的要更强大
Your wife appears to be stronger than we imagined, Mr. Torrance.
有点
Somewhat
太足智多谋了点
more... ...resourceful.
她看起来比你厉害多了
She seems to have got the better of you.
暂时的  格雷迪先生
For the moment, Mr. Grady.
只是暂时的
Only for the moment.
恐怕你得尽可能用最严酷的
I fear you will have to deal with this matter...
方法来摆平此事  托伦斯先生
...in the harshest possible way, mr. Torrance.
恐怕
I fear...
这是唯一的办法
...that is the only thing to do.
我一定能摆平他们的
There's nothing I look forward to...
没问题  格雷迪先生
...with greater pleasure, Mr. Grady.
你保证能办到吗  托伦斯先生
You give your word on that, do you, Mr. Torrance?
我保证
I give you my word.
反过来即谋杀之意
Redrum.
谋杀
丹尼  别喊了
Danny, stop it!
温迪
Wendy
我回来了
I'm home.
快出来  快出来  不管你们在哪儿
Come out, come out, wherever you are.
丹尼  我爬不出去
Danny, I can't get out!
快跑
Run!
快跑  然后躲起来
Run and hide!
快跑
Run!
快点
Quick!
小猪猪们 让我进去吧
Little pigs, little pigs, let me come in.
动画片三只小猪里的一段歌词
让我进去
Not by the hair on your chinny-chin-chin.
我要吹气
Then I'll huff...
吹气
...and I'll puff...
吹翻你的房子
...and I'll blow your house in!
求你了
Please!
不要
Don't!
不要啊
别砍了
Stop it!
强尼来喽
Here's Johnny!
三只小猪中的一只猪叫强尼
有人吗
Hello?
有人在吗
Anybody here?
有人吗
Hello?
有人在吗
Anybody here?
小丹尼
Danny-boy!
丹尼
Danny
Danny...
丹尼
我来了
I'm coming...
丹尼
Danny
派对不错吧
Great party, isn't it?
丹尼
Danny...
我来了
I'm coming!
你逃不了的
You can't get away!
我就在你后面
I'm right behind you!
-妈妈  -丹尼  快过来
- Mommy! - Danny, come here!
妈妈
Mommy.
哪里
Where...?
观景酒店  舞会  1921年 7月4日